nutsandboltsspeedtraining.com 2017-11-07

# Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting www.nutsandboltsspeedtraining dotcom and/or [www.courses.nutsandboltsspeedtraining](http://www.courses.nutsandboltsspeedtraining/) dotcom (the “Sites”). These Sites are operated by Nuts and Bolts Holdings, LLC (“Nuts & Bolts Speed Training”), located at 1526 Alki Ave SW, Apt. 205, Seattle, WA 98116. Your access to and use of these Sites is subject to the following Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”) and all applicable laws. The terms, “we”, “us” and “our” when used in this Privacy Policy mean Nuts & Bolts Speed Training. The terms, “you” and “your” when used in this Privacy Policy mean any user of these Sites.

We understand your concerns about privacy and we want to assure you that Nuts & Bolts Speed Training takes privacy matters seriously. Therefore, we are providing this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.

By submitting your personal information to us through these Sites, you are consenting to the processing of your personal information in the United States.

By accessing or using our Services, you agree to this Privacy Policy.

IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY, PLEASE DO NOT ACCESS OR USE OUR SERVICES.

  1. What type of information does Nuts & Bolts Speed Training collect?

When you use these Sites, we may collect information about you in the following ways:

_Information You Actively Provide._  We collect the personal information you actively provide (using your mouse or keyboard) when you use these Sites. You may choose to provide certain personal information in order to access or use certain features or services of the Sites, such as making a purchase, requesting information, registering on the Sites, filling out a survey, or providing feedback. Such information may include your name, phone number, e-mail, billing address, or mailing address. Where possible, we indicate which fields of information are required and which fields are optional. You can always choose not to provide information, but you may not be able to use a particular service or feature on the Sites.

_Information Sent to Us by Your Web Browser._  We collect information that is sent to us automatically by your web browser. This information typically includes your computer’s IP address, the address of the web page you were visiting when you accessed our Sites, the name of the operating system installed on your computer, the name and version of the browser you are using, the URL of the page from which you linked to our Sites, and the date and time of your visit. The information we receive depends on the settings on your web browser. Please check with the developer of your browser if you want to learn what information the browser sends or how to change your settings. The information provided by your browser does not identify you personally. We use this non-personal information primarily to create statistics that help us improve our Sites and make it more compatible with the technology used by our visitors. We may link this non-personal information with your personal information as we deem necessary for our business purposes.

If we suspect criminal activity, we might share our server logs — which contain visitors’ IP addresses — with the appropriate investigative authorities who could use that information to trace and identify individuals.

  2. Cookies

_Information Collected Using “Cookies” and Other Web Technologies._  We use “cookies,” and similar technologies to collect information and support the functionality of these Sites. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your computer’s hard disk by a web server. Cookies cannot be used to install computer programs or deliver viruses to your computer. We may use cookies to collect information about the ways visitors use our Sites – which pages they visit, which links they use, and how long they stay on each page. We analyze this information (known as “click-stream information”) to better understand our visitors’ interests and needs and to improve the content and functionality of our Sites, and to facilitate the proper functioning of our Sites. We may also use cookies to remember your login name or preferences for your future visits to our Sites, and to improve your experience when using our Sites. We may link the information collected by our cookies to information that identifies you personally and store it with other information we have collected from or about you.

You have the ability to set your browser to reject cookies, however, if you set your browser to reject cookies, you may not be able to use certain features and functionality of these Sites.

  3. Our use of your information

We use personal information you submit to us for various business purposes, such as to process your payment or request for information as applicable. If you provide us with your e-mail address as part of a purchase transaction on our Sites, or if you opt-in to receive communications from Nuts & Bolts Speed Training, we may periodically send you newsletters or e-mails featuring promotions, informing you about new events and services, requesting your feedback, or providing other information we think may be of interest to you. You can remove your e-mail address from our e-mail list at any time by contacting us Taylor@nutsandboltsspeedtraining dot.com or Camille@nutsandboltsspeedtraining dot.com, or clicking on the “unsubscribe” link in every Nuts & Bolts Speed Training e-newsletter.

We use certain non-personal information we collect from you for specific and limited purposes including improving our materials and services, making your browsing experience more efficient and relevant, and for administration of these Sites.

  4. Does Nuts & Bolts Speed Training share the information it receives?

Nuts & Bolts Speed Training may share your information: (i) with third parties who are under obligations of confidentiality with Nuts & Bolts Speed Training; (ii) if Nuts & Bolts Speed Training is required by law to do so; (iii) in the event of a transfer of ownership Nuts & Bolts Speed Training, merger or other similar transaction; or (iv) as otherwise set forth in this Privacy Policy. The following describes some of the ways that your information may be disclosed to third parties:

_Our Service Providers._  We share personal information collected through our Sites with companies and organizations that perform services on our behalf, such as data storage, web hosting services, and order fulfillment companies. These companies and organizations are required by contract to use the personal information we share with them only to perform services on our behalf (and not for their own purposes) and to protect its confidentiality.

_Our Successors._  We may transfer the personal information we collect through the Sites to another company (either an affiliate or an unrelated third party) that has acquired the assets of Nuts & Bolts Speed Training, for example, as the result of a sale, merger, reorganization, dissolution or liquidation. If such a transfer occurs, the acquiring company will “step into our shoes” and collect, use and share your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

_Other Limited Circumstances._  There are other limited circumstances in which we may share the personal information in our databases with unrelated third parties. For example, we may disclose the personal information we collect through the Sites when we, in good faith, believe disclosure is appropriate to comply with the law or a regulatory requirement or to comply with a subpoena or court order; to prevent or investigate a possible crime, such as fraud or identity theft; to enforce a contract; to protect the rights, property or safety of Nuts & Bolts Speed Training, and visitors to our Sites, or to protect the vital interests of our visitors.

_Marketing Purposes._  We rarely (almost never) share your personal information with third parties to use for their own marketing purposes. We pride ourselves on keeping your information private but we may occasionally share your personal information, if we think the products or services they offer would be of extreme interest to you. You may opt-out of receiving such communications at any time contacting us at info at Taylor@nutsandboltsspeedtraining dot.com or Camille@nutsandboltsspeedtraining dot.com

_Third Party Sites._  You may visit other websites, through links on our Sites, which may collect, use and share your information in accordance with their own privacy policies. The information practices of those websites linking from or to our Sites are not covered by this Privacy Policy, and we encourage you to be very cautious before you disclose your information to others.

  5. Accessing and Updating Your Information

You always have the opportunity to review and change the information you provide to us by contacting us at Taylor@nutsandboltsspeedtraining dot.com or Camille@nutsandboltsspeedtraining dot.com.

You may ask to have your account information removed from our active databases and to mark your information as “do not contact.” If you request to be placed on “do not contact” status, although your information will remain in our records, Nuts & Bolts Speed Training will not contact you for any of the purposes set forth in this Privacy Policy or otherwise. We prefer to retain your information and place your information in “do not contact” status rather than deleting your information entirely to ensure that the next time you contact Nuts & Bolts Speed Training, we do not add you to our mailing lists or otherwise contact you as described in this Privacy Policy. However, if you object to this practice and wish to instead have your information completely removed from our database, please send an e-mail to Taylor@nutsandboltsspeedtraining dot.com or Camille@nutsandboltsspeedtraining dot.com with a request that your information be deleted in its entirety rather than marked as “do not contact.”

We keep your personal information only as long as we need it for the purposes for which it was originally collected (or to which you have subsequently consented) or for other legitimate purposes (such as regulatory compliance), or as permitted by applicable law.

  6. Security

We take reasonable precautions to: (i) protect the confidentiality and security of the personal information we collect through these Sites; (ii) ensure that your transactions on our Sites will be safe; and (iii) protect you from unauthorized credit card charges while you make payments on our Sites. Additionally, Nuts & Bolts Speed Training uses physical and electronic security measures to protect your information. However, it is important that you understand, that no website or database is completely secure or “hacker proof.”

  7. Privacy Policy Changes

We are continually improving and adding to the functionality and features of the Sites. As a result of these changes (or changes in the law), we may need to update or revise our Privacy Policy. Accordingly, we reserve the right to update or modify this Privacy Policy, at any time and without prior notice, by posting the revised version of this Privacy Policy on the Sites. Your use of the Sites following any such change constitutes your agreement that all personal information collected from or about you through the Sites after the revised Privacy Policy is posted will be subject to the terms of the revised Privacy Policy.

  8. Transfer of Data Abroad

If you are visiting these Sites from a country other than the countries in which our servers are located (currently the United States), the various communications will necessarily result in the transfer of information across international boundaries. By visiting these Sites and communicating electronically with us, you consent to the processing and transfer of your data as set out in this Privacy Policy.

  9. Governing Law

This Privacy Policy forms part of our Terms and Conditions and as such is governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of Washington in the United States of America without regard to conflicts of a law principles. You hereby consent and waive all objections to jurisdiction of the federal and state courts of the state of Washington and to venue therein.

If you have further questions about this Privacy Policy, comments on how we can improve your Sites experience, or if you need help or have a data privacy complaint, please do not hesitate to email us at Taylor@nutsandboltsspeedtraining dot.com or Camille@nutsandboltsspeedtraining dot.com.

You may also contact us at:

Nuts and Bolts Holdings LLC

1526 Alki Ave SW, Apt. 205, Seattle, WA 98116
